unitednude.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy | United Nude

### 1.   What we collect & how we use your information

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

Additional information that we may ask for:

  1. Date of birth: So that we can send you birthday treats!
  2. Gender: So that we can send you the correct product information.
  3. Contact history: Provide customer service support and so that we can train our staff to ensure we always give the best service to you.
  4. Purchase History so that we can pull up information on your previous purchases in case there are any issues or in case you have any questions or problems.

We collect your email address in order to:

  1. Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  2. Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  3. Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
  4. Send newsletters (only if you have subscribed to our mailing list).

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at [customerservice@unitednude.com](mailto:customerservice@unitednude.com) or follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL newsletter correspondence.

### 2.   What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  1. Internal record keeping.
  2. We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  3. To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  4. To improve our website in order to provide you with the best shopping experience.
  5. To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  6. To quickly process your transactions.
  7. To follow up with you after correspondence (email or phone inquiries)

### 3.   Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online..

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of trusted employees who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

### 4.   How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### We use cookies to:

  1. Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  2. Keep track of advertisements.
  3. Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

#### If users disable cookies in their browser:

If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the site.

#### Third-party disclosure

 We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

#### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. 

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website marketing.

#### Opting out of google advertising:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page.

Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### 5.   Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### 6.   Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  1. Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.
  2. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at customerservice@unitednude.com

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at customerservice@unitednude.com as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### 7.   List of cookies we collect

### The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store. Cookie declaration last updated on 25/05/2018 by [Cookiebot](https://www.cookiebot.com/ "Cookiebot - The EU Cookie Law Solution"):

Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.

**Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose                                                         **

| 

**Expiry       **

| 

**Type**  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
__cfduid

| 

workable.com

| 

Used by the content network, Cloudflare, to identify trusted web traffic.

| 

1 year

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
CookieConsent

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Stores the user's cookie consent state for the current domain

| 

1 year

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.

**Name                                              **

| 

**Provider                    **

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Expiry               **

| 

**Type**  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
@@History/@@scroll|# [x2]

| 

unitednude.com  
vars.hotjar.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTML Local Storage  
  
_dc_gtm_UA-#

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Used by Google Tag Manager to control the loading of a Google Analytics script tag.

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_ga

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.

| 

2 years

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_gat

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Used by Google Analytics to throttle request rate

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_gid

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Registers a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how the visitor uses the website.

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.

**Name**

| 

**Provider                                                   **

| 

**Purpose  **

| 

**Expiry .                           **

| 

**  Type                          **  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
_gac_UA-#

| 

unitednude.com  .  

| 

Stores information about ad campaigns from Google Adwords to show targeted ads to the visitor.

| 

3 months

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_hjIncludedInSample

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Determines if the user's navigation should be registered in a certain statistical place holder.

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
0

| 

adform.net

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
ads/ga-audiences

| 

google.com

| 

Used by Google AdWords to re-engage visitors that are likely to convert to customers based on the visitor's online behaviour across websites.

| 

Session

| 

Pixel Tracker  
  
ads/user-lists/#

| 

google.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

Pixel Tracker  
  
cid

| 

adform.net

| 

Optimises ad display based on the user's movement combined and various advertiser bids for displaying user ads.

| 

2 months

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
collect

| 

google analytics.com

| 

Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels.

| 

Session

| 

Pixel Tracker  
  
fr

| 

facebook.com

| 

Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers.

| 

3 months

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
i

| 

yandex.ru

| 

Unclassified

| 

10 years

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
IDE 

| 

doubleclick.net

| 

Used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.

| 

1 year

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
MUID

| 

bing.com

| 

Used widely by Microsoft as a unique user ID. The cookie enables user tracking by synchronising the ID across many Microsoft domains.

| 

1 year

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
MUIDB

| 

bing.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

1 year

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
test_cookie

| 

doubleclick.net

| 

Used to check if the user's browser supports cookies.

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
tr

| 

facebook.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

Pixel Tracker  
  
uid

| 

adform.net

| 

Registers a unique user ID that recognises the user's browser when visiting websites that use the same ad network. The purpose is to optimise display of ads based on the user's movements and various ad providers' bids for displaying user ads.

| 

2 months

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
watch/43202149

| 

yandex.ru

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

Pixel Tracker  
  
yabs-sid

| 

yandex.ru

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
yandexuid

| 

yandex.ru

| 

Unclassified

| 

10 years

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
yp

| 

yandex.ru

| 

Unclassified

| 

10 years

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
Unclassified cookies are cookies that we are in the process of classifying, together with the providers of individual cookies.

**Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Expiry**

| 

**Type**  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
_flowbox

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

29 days

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_uetsid

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_workable_visitor

| 

workable.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

20 years

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_ym_isad

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_ym_metrika_enabled

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_ym_metrika_enabled_43202149

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
_ym_uid

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

2 years

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
external_no_cache

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
FPC_PRODUCT_VIEWED

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
frontend

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
frontend_cid

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie  
  
metrika_enabled

| 

unitednude.com

| 

Unclassified

| 

Session

| 

HTTP Cookie
